&GT；&GT；Kyle Simpson：所以有拐角案例，我们知道这是现实，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: So there are corner cases, we know that that's the reality,
有拐角处的案子。
there were corner cases.
我们不处理任何语言的角落情况，但最重要的是JavaScript，
We don't deal with corner cases in any language but least of all, JavaScript,
通过简单地避免它。
by simply avoiding it.
你不能为了绕过几个角落的案子而回避整个机制。
You don't avoid the whole mechanism just to get around a couple of corner cases.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：您必须采用一种编码风格，使您的类型和
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: You have to adopt a coding style that makes your types and
这些类型的值简单明了，
the values that are in those types plain and obvious,
这是唯一有效的方法。
that's the only effective way to do this.
有些人甚至使用整个类型的系统，并且
Some people goes so far as to used whole type systems, and
我们稍后会讨论这个问题，比如打印稿和其他东西。
we'll get into that a little bit later like TypeScript and stuff.
我认为你不必走那么远，但你可以采用一种编码风格
I don't think you have to go that far but you can adopt a coding style which makes
你正在做的类型更加明显。
the kinds of types that you're doing much more obvious.
我声称一个高质量的JavaScript程序必须
I make the claim that a quality JavaScript program is going to have to
接受强制。
embrace coercion.
您必须确保每个操作中涉及的类型都是明确的。
You have to make sure that the types involved in every operation are clear.
顺便说一句，这意味着你不应该设计所有这些
And by the way that means that you shouldn't be designing all these
多态函数，可以采用任何类型的值和
polymorphic functions that can take any sort of value and
根据价值做15件不同的事情。
do 15 different things based upon the value.
当你这样做的时候你是在要求强制的问题
You're asking for coercion problems when you do that and
然后用纸盖住它们，但我使用了三元组，我使用了三元组等于。
then papering over them, but I used the triple, I used the triple equals.
为什么不只设计一个只接受数字和
Why not just design a function that only takes numbers and
然后创建另一个只接受字符串的函数？
then make another function that only takes strings?
或创建一个接受数字和字符串的函数，以及
Or make a function that takes numbers and strings, and
很明显只能是这两种，而且
it's very clear it can only be those two types, and
我知道在数字和字符串之间我必须担心哪些拐角处的情况。
I know what corner cases I have to worry about between numbers and strings.
我们可以选择更明显的方式来管理我们的类型，
We can choose to be more obvious about how we manage our types,
我们有多重载，我们使我们的代码有多形态化。
how much we overload, how polymorphic we make our code.
我们可以选择解决更多的问题，也可以选择退出问题。
We can opt in to more problems or opt out of problems as a result.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我希望你在这里得到的最大收获是这些
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: Biggest takeaway that I want you to get here is that these
是你的计划的事实，它是在你的职权范围内决定多少或
are fact of your programs and it is within your purview to decide how much or
这些事实对你的影响有多小。
how little you're gonna be affected by those facts.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：这并不是说我们问题的唯一解决方案是
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: That is not to suggest that the only solution to our problem is
一切都必须严格，一切都是完全静态输入的。
that everything have to rigidly, everything's completely statically typed.
我们基本上只需要去编写Java或C Plus，这样我们就可以得到一些
We have to just basically go write Java or C Plus Plus so that we get some
有点像声音类型系统，这是对这个问题的反应，
kind of like sound type system, that is a reaction to this problem,
我认为这不是必要的反应。
it is not the the reaction I think that is necessary.
所以我在这里宣扬的信息是你可以学习这些系统，
So the message I'm preaching here is you can learn these systems,
适当地使用它们，并使它们在代码中变得明显。
use them appropriately and make them obvious in your code.
&gt；&gt；Kyle Simpson：我不认为这种打字系统是弱点，
&gt;&gt; Kyle Simpson: I do not think that this typing systems are weaknesses,
实际上，我认为这是JavaScript最强的品质之一。
I actually think this is one of JavaScript's strongest qualities.
这是一个无名英雄，我认为这是为什么JavaScript是
It's an unsung hero, I think it's one of the reasons why JavaScript is
它今天是无处不在的语言，因为它一直如此
the ubiquitous language that it is today because it has been so
适合这么多不同的用例。
palatable to so many different use cases.
第一个真正的多范式语言，以及它之所以拥有的一个很大的原因
The first truly multi-paradigm language and a big reason why it has
能够在多范式中生存是因为它的类型系统。
been able to survive multi-paradigm is because of its type system.
这与我的每一个同龄人和
And that's completely opposite from what every one of my peers and
你听过的其他一切。
everything else that you've ever heard.
其他人总是告诉你这是JavaScript最糟糕的部分
Everybody else has always told you this is the worst part of JavaScript and
我会坚定地说这是JavaScript最好的部分之一。
I'm gonna put my foot down and say it's one of the best parts of JavaScript.
如果你不使用它，你的程序就会错过
And if you're not using it, your programs are missing out